rightstart.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Rightstart.com

Updated January 16, 2014

Please note that we have modified our Privacy Policy. All changes shall be in full force and in effect as of August 28, 2013. Under the revised Privacy Policy terms, we may provide your identifiable customer information, including name, address and email addresses, to our "select partners," reputable companies or organizations whose products or services may interest you. Our sharing of this information is not an endorsement of products or services that are offered. We may also disclose personally identifiable and/or aggregate customer information under the following circumstances: (a) when required by law; (b) to protect site users, or our employees, related third parties, or property; and/or (c) in the event of a bankruptcy, insolvency, merger, or acquisition.

  * Commitment to Privacy
  * What Information Do You Gather About Me?
  * How Secure is My Information?
  * What about My Account?
  * How does RightStart.com Recognize Me?
  * Does RightStart.com Use Cookies?

##### Commitment to Privacy

NOTICE: Our Privacy Policy changed as of August 28, 2013.

We value you as a customer, and we know your concerned about protecting your privacy online. Our mission is to inform you of our policies for collecting, sharing, disseminating and securing customer information online.

The site contains links to other sites as a convenience and for informational purposes only. RightStart.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such Web sites.

Back to Top

##### What Information Do You Gather About Me?

This privacy policy explains how we collect and use customer information gathered at this web site in order to conduct our business, inform customers about our products and provide customer service. Examples of personal information we collect include: your full name, home address, billing address, email address and phone number.

_What we gather_ : We need your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, billing phone number, shipping phone number and credit card number to process and ship your order. We will email you to confirm your order and keep you updated on your order status. If we have a question about your order, we may contact you by either email or by phone. For example, for your security we may call you to verify your credit card information on a large purchase.

In addition, we use your information and cookies to recommend products and features based on your shopping and purchasing history, to personalize our newsletters if you choose to subscribe, to maintain your account and to improve your shopping experience or to notify you of any updates to our Privacy Policy.

_Who we share it with_ : We share customer information with select partners, contractors, subsidiaries and related entities that also may use the information to, for example, recommend products and features based on your past purchases, improve your shopping experience, or check on the quality of your customer service experience. We also share customer information with service providers to conduct business on behalf of our company and its affiliated entities, such as payment authorization and processing companies, customer service providers, drop ship vendors and shippers. In addition, we share customer information with other companies or organizations whose products or services may interest you. In these cases, we may share or cross-reference personally identifiable information to allow these companies or organizations to contact you regarding their products or services or to check on the quality of your customer service experience. In addition, should you choose to accept an offer from a third party marketed through our site; we will pass your relevant personal information, including name, address and email address, to that third party which may have its own privacy policy which describes how it uses your personal information once you subscribe to the service. In the event of a bankruptcy, insolvency, merger or acquisition, customer information, including personal information, may be transferred. We may also disclose aggregate, non-identifiable customer information (such as number of visits or average order amounts) to advertisers or other third parties.

Back to Top

NO THIRD PARTY IS AUTHORIZED TO ACT ON OUR BEHALF REGARDING THE UPDATING OF ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. IF YOU RECEIVE A REQUEST TO UPDATE YOUR RIGHTSTART.COM ACCOUNT FROM A THIRD PARTY PLEASE NOTIFY US. 

_Information about kids_ : The RightStart.com web site is designed for adults who make purchases for children. RightStart.com doesn't knowingly solicit or collect information from children who are 13 or younger.

When we email our newsletter, it includes prominently displayed instructions that show you how to unsubscribe from the newsletter. If your child subscribes to the RightStart.com newsletter without your knowledge, simply follow the instructions, and unsubscribe immediately. If you want more information about children's privacy online, you can consult the "Consumer Protection" page on the Federal Trade Commission site.

_The RightStart.com Newsletter_ : If you want to receive email newsletters from RightStart.com with updates on sales, promotions and new arrivals, you must subscribe or place an order with the company.

When we launch a new newsletter, we may email it to you if you subscribe to the RightStart.com newsletter and if your buying patterns indicate that the information in the newsletter might interest you.

All newsletter subscribers have the option to opt-out from receiving RightStart.com newsletters. Each newsletter prominently displays a link you can use to unsubscribe at any time. We also include the email address you used when you signed up for the newsletter, so you know which address to enter when you unsubscribe.

_Sweepstakes or special promotions_ : You may have noticed some of the sweepstakes or special promotions we may feature occasionally on this web site or in email communications to you. By participating in a sweepstakes or special promotion you will also be subject to and hereby agree to abide by the official rules of the sweepstakes or special promotion and any third party policies. Unless otherwise prohibited by law, we may use personal information submitted during a promotion or sweepstakes to contact you. We may also add your email address to our customer newsletter mailing list unless you choose not to subscribe by checking a box to opt-out. In addition, by participating in any sweepstakes or special promotions you agree to give RightStart.com complete rights to content submitted (when applicable) and allow us to publish the content as we see fit.

Back to Top

_Referral programs_ : We may from time to time offer you the opportunity to earn rewards by referring friends to a web site owned or operated by us or an affiliated company. Participation in a Referral Program may require you to submit personal information about you and your friends, such as name and email address. By participating in a Referral Program you agree to receive communications from us and/or from our partners that operate and maintain the Referral Program both during and after your participation in the program. Please note that by signing up for and/or participating in such programs you are also subject to all rules governing the applicable referral program.

_Contacting RightStart.com Customer Service_ : If you contact our customer service, we may use your name, email address, phone number and order history to answer your question as quickly as possible. On occasion, we may contact you later to verify information or to check on the quality of your Customer Service contact.

_Legal requests_ : We may release customer account or other information if we're advised that release is necessary to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property and safety of our company, its affiliates, customers, employees or others. We may also exchange information with companies and organizations or law enforcement for loss prevention and credit risk reduction.

Back to Top

_Other communications_ : We may collect information you have provided to us from surveys, social media, the Right Start Blog, third party apps and by other means of communication. By providing your information to us through these platforms and other communications, you are agreeing to this privacy policy.

##### How Secure is My Information?

Notice that the "http" portion of the web site address in your Internet browser changes to "https." The "s" stands for "secure." In addition, there may also be other visual indications such as a lock symbol, green highlighting and other indicators of a secure Web page. Refer to you Internet browser's "help" guide for more information about indicators of secure Web browsing. Some browsers let you know that you're moving in or out of a secure area by notifying you with a special pop-up window that requires you to click "ok" before continuing. 

_Protecting your password_ : We also attempt to limit unauthorized access to your account. If you forget your password, you can create a new one. You can do your part to protect your personal information by keeping your password protected and making sure you log off completely if you share a computer.

Back to Top

##### What about My Account?

_Creating an account_ : Unlike many e-commerce sites, we don't require our customers to create an account and keep information on file with us. However, creating an account makes it even faster and easier to shop at our site and allows us to communicate with you more effectively.

RightStart.com will never ask for your credit card number other than when you make a payment during a transaction.

If you don't want to keep your credit card information on file when you create an account, that's fine, you can re-enter your credit card number each time you checkout. 

Back to Top

##### How does RightStart.com Recognize Me?

We automatically recognize your Internet Service Provider (ISP) and your operating system. We also use cookies to monitor your shopping activity on our site. We may use this information to determine the most popular products and pages on our site and to enhance our marketing efforts and activities. This helps us make changes to improve your shopping experience.

If you enter this site from one of our affiliate sites, you may notice a special code at the end of our Web address as you move through our site. That tells us which affiliate site you entered through. We may give that affiliate credit for any purchase you make.

Back to Top

##### Does RightStart.com Use Cookies?

Yes. A "cookie" is a special identifier. Web sites transfer cookies to your hard drive through your Web browser. Cookies help us identify you when you visit one of our sites. For example, if you have a discount coupon or certificate from us or an affiliate site, this information may be stored in your cookie. We don't store your password or any personal information in your cookie. If you want to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, set your browser options to let you know when you receive a new cookie, or turn off your cookies completely. You can find out how by reading the "help" portion of your toolbar on most browsers. Remember, however, that if you turn off the cookies feature, you will not be able to take advantage of all the special features we offer.

_Modifications to Privacy Policy_ : We may make modifications to this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check this web site for periodic updates. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of this page by its effective date.

_Acceptance of Terms by Customer_ : Please note that accessing this web site or otherwise providing any information to us constitutes your acceptance of the terms set forth in our Privacy Policy and all other Terms of Use. 

_Governing Law_ : Any disputes arising under this Agreement will be resolved in accordance with the Terms of Use. 

Back to Top
